下面介绍构建Sunshine方式变化的概况
Here's an overview of the changes we're going to be making to Sunshine.
我们会跟着这张图的引导来完成我们的编码练习
We'll continue to refer to this map as we move these coding exercises.
这张图中有许多条目我们之前没有讨论过
There are lots of terms in this map that we haven't discussed before
例如数据库常量  内容提供者以及DB Helper
such as database contract, content provider, and DB Helper.
这里的每一个块都代表着一个模块化数据存储
Each one of these blocks represents a section of our modular
解决方案的选项
data storage solution.
我们从根据一个协议来定义我数据存储开始
We start by defining our data storage in terms of a contract.
我们一会儿将用SQLite来实现这个数据库
We then implement the database using SQLite.
最后我们在UI和数据存储之间放置一个
And finally, we layer a fundamental Android class between our UI and
叫做内容提供者的基础Android类
the data storage called a content provider.
最终  用这种方式构建数据存储可以使Sunshine
Ultimately, building our data storage in this way allows Sunshine to leverage
充分利用强大的Android框架
powerful Android frameworks.
在我们实现每一部分的时候我们将会讲解更多的详细信息
We'll explain all of this in more detail as we implement each section.
让我们现在就开始吧
Let's get started.